{
    "id": "f68afc6014e94782889f818b78d9f539",
    "title": "Personal And Reflexive Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "It is ………………….. car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ded815299ef4a54ae217d6b9dd2b199"
        },
        {
            "question": "That coat is …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca4b49808c5242289f5e8cfb76b9f81f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ……………….. party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "his",
                "him",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e33f1cd3c17340179f7d36938a8a3d59"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is quite fond of praising ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "herself",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7df00bbf42424ad5baabc47adae7fdcf"
        },
        {
            "question": "That must be ……………….. dog.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "their",
                "theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "43f7323df83d43dfb02b57edc0014b28"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must have a word with ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "he",
                "him",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dd8396bbf2254fa3afbc36f1ba62b41a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He did it …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "himself"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d284f278fe1d4aadb7d4e10f1dc795d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Whose bag is this?’ ‘It’s …………………’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ed6ae5ded2724c63a2b5ca7bf83dde39"
        },
        {
            "question": "My dog is an Alsatian. ………………… is a Doberman.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Their",
                "Theirs"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06bd98fd69ed481082bb40463dbc59a2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………… took the baby to the hospital.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her",
                "hers",
                "herself"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d06b3f5231b54b208b79e0e6fb4710c3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t believe ………………. story.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "your",
                "yours"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "81b3880dc27a4a9bb1f1ee5ae0d62864"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mind ………………….. own business.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you",
                "your"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15bc6280cf624b00a7f7330df7212c59"
        },
        {
            "question": "I saw it with …………………. own eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "my",
                "mine"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4f4216adb8d04b11ae2f9ff9b81a76dc"
        }
    ]
}